________________________________

Precisely Portal Texture Pack: 

by carlotta4th

________________________________

PERMISSIONS: You're welcome to modify the packs to fit your own needs/dungeons/etc, but you cannot make profit off of the textures themselves, claim the textures as your own, or post them without giving credit and linking back to the originals. Thank you!
Texture pack link: http://www.minecraftforum.net/topic/158542-16x-32x12-precisely-portal-and-modified-portal/#Index


Directions to install the texture pack:
________________________________

Easy:
1. Open your world in minecraft and click "Options" "Resource Packs."
2. "Open Resource Pack Folder"
3. Copy/Drag the Downloaded Folder in.

More involved:
1. Use your computers search function ("find" or "search") and type in "Run"
2. Open run and type: %appdata%/.minecraft/resourcepacks
3. Drag the texture pack zip file into this folder
4. Open a minecraft world, "options," then "resourcepacks."
5. The pack should be there, enjoy!



CREDITS:
________________________________

-Minecraft is property of Mojang and Notch, Portal is property of Aperture Science and Valve Corporation. Respective credit is applied as such.
-The first portal texture pack for minecraft was "Portal meets Minecraft" by Cosine. THIS pack was the first Beta/survival mode Portal pack, and it is a continuation of Cosine's alpha pack (with permission).

CREDIT FOR SPECIFIC TEXTURES/ANIMATIONS:
-Lava "goo" animation -MC Forum: Restcoser
-Command Block (orange version) -MC Forum: Sayomi_Inoue